UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files 6000/050
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Local 10 and Local 23-25 Files
1940-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees
UNITE
UNITE Local 10
UNITE Local 23-25
6000/050
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Reports, pamphlets, correspondence.
8240660
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 12, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 14, 2014
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5780/001: ILGWU. Local 10 minutes 5780/001 mf: ILGWU. Local 10. Microfilm 5780/008: ILGWU. Local 10 dues books 5780/011: ILGWU. Local 10. Managers' correspondence 5780/012: ILGWU. Local 10. Managers' correspondence 5780/053: ILGWU. Local 105 records 5780/053 AV: ILGWU. Local 105 audio recordings 5780/053 P: ILGWU. Local 105 photographs 5780/059: ILGWU. Local 23-25 records 5780/059 P: ILGWU. Local 23-25 photographs 5780/059 PUBS: ILGWU. Local 23-25 publications 5780/094: ILGWU. Local 10 membership record books 5780/095: ILGWU. Local 23-25 records 5780/095 G: ILGWU. Local 23-25 graphics 5780/131: ILGWU. Local 10 records 6000/024: UNITE. Local 23-25 Records 6000/024 AV: UNITE. Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials 6000/024 MB: Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). Local 23-25. Memorabilia. 6000/024 P: UNITE. Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/024 PUBS: Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). Local 23-25. Publications. 6000/050 AV: UNITE. Local 10 and Local 23-25 Audio-Visual Materials. 6000/050 MB: UNITE. Local 10 and Local 23-25 Memorabilia. 6000/050 P: UNITE. Local 10 and Local 23-25 Photographs 6000/050 PUBS: UNITE. Local 10 and Local 23-25 Publications. 6200/005: UNITE HERE. Local 23-25. Files. 6200/005 MB: UNITE HERE. Local 23-25. Memorabilia. 6200/005 P: UNITE HERE. Local 23-25 Photographs all series 6000 collections
8240660
- Executive Board Minutes (Box 1)
  - Ex Bd Meeting, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of the Executive Board Meeting Thursday, December 19, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Local 23-25, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Scope and Contents
    1 Floppy Disc
  - Executive Board Meeting Local 23-25 UNITE!, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1998 UAG (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1998 Ex. Bd. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1998 Bd Sign-ins (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1999 Exec. Board (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 2000 Executive Board (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 2001 Exec. Board (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Fernwood in the Poconos Seminar 2/23-25/01 Misc- Board, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Local 23-25 Elections 3/14/2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - UAG 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NY Joint Board (ILG), 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Ex Bd. Stuff, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board 2002 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - 2003 Executive Board (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Immigrant Workers Freedom Ride, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Installation Meeting 4/26/01, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Exec Bd Mtg. 1/02, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Exec Bd 2/28/02, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Exec Bd 3/02, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Exec. Bd April 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - May 2002 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - June Exec Bd, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Exec Bd Sept, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Oct' 02 Exec. Bd, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Exec Bd Nov 2002 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Exec Bd 1/30/03, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Exec Bd 3/03, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Exec Bd 4/2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Exec. May 2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Executive Board 7/31/03, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Minute Book, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - CWE 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Worker Education, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - 2002-2003 Worker Ed. Program (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - CWE 2004-5 Budget, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Worker Education, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Collective Agreement w/ Metropolitan Area Apparel Assoc. Inc. (1992) (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Executive Board Meeting January 20, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Resolution of Local 89-22-1, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Manuals, Song Books, Contract Negotiations (Box 2)
  - Steward Update (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Resources for UNITE! Union Reps, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Basic Steward Training Manual (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Basic Steward Training Manual 2001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Basic Steward Training Manual Copy 2, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Basic Steward Training Manual Copy 3, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Local Campaign Tool Kit, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Song Book (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Song Book: Negro Spirituals, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Song Book, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Song Book: Happy Holidays (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Agenda, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Song Book (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Song Book (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Song Book: Rubye Jones Chorus (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Memory (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - ILGWU, 1976-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Labor Papers, 1990-1999 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - No Sweat, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - UNITE Chorus. Info and Meeting R. Jones, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Malcolm Dodds 3/15/96, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Chorus Songs and Music Info., 1993 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - UNITE Chorus (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Hector Martins Chorus DIR, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Special Folder for Hector Director of UNITE Chorus (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Malcolm Dodds, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Winer Case, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Manufacturer Association Contracts [Folder 1 of 3] 2004-2007 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Manufacturer Association Contacts [Folders 2 of 3] 2004-2007 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Manufacturer Association Contracts [Folder 3 of 3] 2004-2007 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Contract Negotiations (Box 3)
  - Collective Agreement, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - UNITE, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - '96 Retail Campaign, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Consolidation Plan and Merger, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - New York Sampleroom Collective Bargaining Agreement, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 2001 Contractor Benefits (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - GBA Letters on Benefits, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Contract Negotiations, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Contract Negotiations 2001 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Collective Agreement, 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - UNITE!, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - GBA Contract 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Floppy Disc
  - B & C Fashions, Inc., 2002-2005 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Greater Blouse, Skirt and Undergarment Association Inc., 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Metropolitan Apparel Mfg. Association, Inc., 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Sportswear Apparel Assoc. Inc., 2001-2004 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - '97 Independents, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - '97 Contract Memoranda (MOU), 1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Labor Day Parade, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Contract Negotiations Meeting, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Local 23-25 UNITE, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Contract Negotiations 1997 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Contract Negotiations [Folder 1 of 3], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Contract Negotiations [Folder 2 of 3], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Contract Negotiations [Folder 3 of 3], 1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Contracts Expiring 2004 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Local 10 Health and Vacation Fund, Scholarships, Real Estate Issues, Fernwood (Box 4)
  - Local 10 Health and Vacation Fund Rules and Regulations 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Local 10 Health and Vacation Fund Minutes 2001 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local 10 health and Vacation fund Minutes [Folder 1 of 2] 2002 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Local 10 Health and Vacation Fund Minutes [Folder 2 of 2] 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Local 10 Health and Vacation Fund Minutes 2003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship Award Ceremony 95. Textbook Scholarship 8/16/95, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Scholarship 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - MIS. (Scholarship 1995) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship 95 Annual, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - UNITE! College Textbook Scholarship 2006 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1997 Mis - Students Letters other Informations of Scholarship App. Labels (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 1997 Problems cases (Applicants + Reject letter ( 2nd Part of Application form) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 1996 Scholarship Mis. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1996 Scholarship Committee File (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 1996 Letters to College Advisor (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - 1996 National Schedule (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - 1996 Scholarship Awards (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1996 Scholarship Reward (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 2001 Renewal (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 2001 Scholarship (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 2001 Scholarship (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Scholarship 2002 Award (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 2002 Scholarship + Renewal (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 2002 Scholarship (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - "Making it Right" 11/5/2002 @ Crowne Pl. Times Square (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Health US Dol, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - NO SWEAT. Compliance Workshop, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - '04 Atlantic City - Local 54, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - UAW Casinos/Misc., 2007 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Meira Bernstein, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Real Estate Issues [Folder 1 of 4], 2000 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Real Estate Issues [Folder 2 of 4], 2000 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Real Estate Issues [Folder 3 of 4], 2000-2008 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Real Estates Issues [Folder 4 of 4], 2000 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Fernwood [Folder 1 of 2] 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Fernwood [Folder 2 of 2] 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Planning, Manufacturers, 911 (Box 5)
  - TRA., 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - TRA, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - GHI (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - GHI (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - IL Benefits Changes - Local 23-25, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Local 23-25 and Local 10, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Contract Meetings, June 3-4, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - National Association of Blouse MFRS, Inc., 2004 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Opening 3-22-04, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Local 102 Nego., 2004 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Contract 2004 Planning (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Letters Notice 2004 Negotiation Meeting (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Arbitrator 2006 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Affordable Leather, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Arlington Hat Co., Inc. & NY Metro-Politan Area Jt. Bd. Local 155, UNITE HERE, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - 2004-2007 Manufacturer Association (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - 2004-2007 Manufacturer Association Contracts with Local 23-25 and Local 10 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Metropolitan Area Apparel Association, Inc., 2004-2007 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - 2004-2007 Manufacturer Association Contracts with Local 23-25 and Local 10 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - UNITE HERE!, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - NJ Shops Transferred to my MAJB - 2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Local 23-25 NY Metropolitan Area Jt. Board. & W & M Headwear, Corp., 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Hornick - 2006 Negotiations (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Jobbers' Memorandum of Agreement 5/3/04, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - 2004 Contractor MOA (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - NES Enterprises, Inc. & Local 155, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Committees - Members, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Agreements, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Union Health Center, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Benefits Counseling Unit, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Wage Subsidy Programs - Earn Fair, CWE, GIDC, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Sept 11th Relief Checks Asian Ame. Federation of NY, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Wold Vision Program, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Made in NY, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - The September 11 Fund, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Shops Lists - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Questionnaires, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - "911 Relief Fund GIDC Proposal", 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - UHC ~ 911, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - 2002 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- 911, Immigration, Activities, Procurement (Box 6)
  - "911 Relief Fund Proposal", 2001-2003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Shops List, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - "UNITE 911 Solidarity Fund", 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Uniting for the American Dream, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Restoring the American Dream, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Chinese Laborists Emails, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - UNITE!, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Immigration - 2006-7 Notes, 2006-2007 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Local 23-25 UNITE & The United Health Center, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - 2000 OSHA Testimony (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - UNITE HERE Magazine - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - ICFTU, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - ICFTU, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Keeping Coverage, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - PAC Fundraising Guide 2005 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Politics '04, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - UNITE Code of Ethical Conduct, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Sidney Hillman Foundation, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Medicare Part D, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Social Security Toolkit 2005 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Retiree Activities, 2006-2009 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Smithsonian 2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 3-12-04 Chinese New Year Party, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - 2005 Chinese New Year (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - 2005 Chinese News Clips (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - NYC CLC Immigrant Commission, 2000-2002 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Uniform Campaign 05-06, 2005-2006 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Uniforms - 2004 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1999 California Joint Resp Law (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Procurement Bill 2000 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - UNITE!, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Procurement NYS - Schneiderman, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Talking Points for May Chen at ATU Meeting (4/25/02), 2002 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - CAF 2002 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 4/25/01 Proc. Over-ride Rally, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 11-21-00 Procurement Hearing, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Aug. 7 Apparel Campaign, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - KC Accessories, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Shop and Association Books, Triangle Fire Resolution, Computer Media (Box 7)
  - Contract 1997 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - The Garment Center: Still in Fashion, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Newsletters, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Labor Day 2002 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - ILGWU - 100 yrs., 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - History of Local 23-25, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Memorandum or Support, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - UNITE! 2004 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Health & Safety, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Garment Industry Info, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Local 23-25 UNITE!, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - savethegarmentcenter.com, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Contract 2004 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Contract 2007 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Contract 2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Local 23-25 Papers, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Membership Meeting I.S. 131, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - UNITE Folders, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Green Folder, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Trade Dr - CAFTA, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Textbook Scholarship, 1997-2004 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Local 23-25 Text Book Scholarship, Thur, 8/10 @FIT, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 9/11 - Relief Efforts, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1990 Shop Rep Training (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - UNITE!, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Doris Ling-Cohan, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - May Chen's Calendar, Democratic National Convention 1996 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 2000 Midtown Survey (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Robert Pauls Garment District, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - May Chen, UNITY Convention 2003 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - "Welcome to the Union!" New Members Information Kit, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - China Press, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Posters, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Yale Strike - 2003 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Floppy Disc Files 1995-2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- UNITE! Education & Mobilization (Box 8, Folder 2)
- State of New York Legislative Resolution, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Local 10 Master Book Shop Listing & Association Listing, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Shop Book a/o 1/20/99, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)